eastcoasthavoc.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy – EastCoastHavoc

Privacy Statement for EastCoastHavoc

We, the Staff Members of EastCoastHavoc, have created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following data below discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for EastCoastHavoc.com.

Advertisers 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Policy For Minors

EastCoastHavoc.com does not allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to register for our services. We may momentarily capture personally identifiable information for purposes of determining whether a user is over the age of thirteen (13) and thus qualifies to use our services. When the user is under the age of thirteen (13), submitted information is automatically deleted.

Public Forums 

This site contains links to other sites. EastCoastHavoc is not responsible for privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. This site may link to chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups at times. Please remember that any information that is disclosed via these outlets become public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may [contact us](http://www.eastcoasthavoc.com/contact-us/) via e-mail.
